Guide to the William Miller Abrahams Papers, ca. 1945-1998
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1. Editorial files
  - Subseries A. Authors
    - Howard, Donald Roy. Chaucer: correspondence (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Howard, Donald Roy. ts of Howard's observation of White night riot, May 21, 1979, photocopies of newspaper obituaries (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Howard, Donald Roy.: journal articles by Howard, and Harder, Bernard D. regarding Chaucer, photocopied ts, Chaucer: the life and it's work (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Howard, Donald Roy. Chaucer: contracts, phtocopied ts of proposal, photocopied ts of Chaucer chronology, miscellaneous photocopied material (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Howard, Donald Roy. Chaucer: editorial material (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Howard, Donald Roy. Chaucer: photocopied reviews (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Howard, Donald Roy. Chaucer: photographs, photocopied ts of curriculum vitae, 5.25'' floppy disks,correspondence (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Ilyin, Olga. White road: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Ingram, Kevin. Rebel (for action's sake): photocopied ts (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Ingram, Kevin. Rebel: photocopied ts, pp 1-158 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Ingram, Kevin. Rebel: photocopied ts, pp 159-327 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Ingram, Kevin. Rebel: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Isherwood, Christopher, and Bachardi, Don. Portraits and people: correspondence, editorial material (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Diane. Le divorce: correspondence, editorial material (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, Diane. Le divorce: photocopy of article by Johnson, photocopies of reviews, photocopies of reviews of previous works (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Johnson, Greg. Joyce Carol Oates, a biography: correspondence (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Nora. Perfect together. correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Richard. Living in the 25th hour: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Jose, Nicholas. Avenue of eternal peace: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Kael, Pauline. All the way with the movies: correspondence, editorial material (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Kael, Pauline. 5001 nights at the movies; et al: correspondence relating to several works, 1975-1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Kael, Pauline. 5001 nights at the movies: editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Kael, Pauline. For keeps: ts of introductory material, correspondence (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Kael, Pauline. For keeps: editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Kael, Pauline. Hooked: correspondence (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Kael, Pauline. Hooked: editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Kael, Pauline. Movie love: editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Kael, Pauline. Reeling: photocopied ts of front material, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Kael, Pauline. Wearing the quick away: carboned ts of unpublished[?] short play (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Kael, Pauline. When the lights go down: editorial material, photocopies of reviews, articles (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Kael, Pauline.: photocopied ts of front material for an unidentified work, miscellaneous editorial material (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - King, Tabitha. Survivor: several pages of edited ts, editorial material and correspondence, photocopies of reviews (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Knowles, John. A stolen past: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Knowles, John. A vein of riches: correspondence, editorial material (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Knowles, John. The private life of Axie Reed: photocopied ts of first chapter, photocopied ts of several short stories (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Knowles, John. The private life of Axie Reed: correspondence (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Knowles, John. The private life of Axie Reed: editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Knowles, John. Peace breaks out: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Kornblatt, Joyce R. Breaking bread (in progresss): photocopied ts (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Kornblatt, Joyce R. Breaking bread: photocopied proofs, pp 1-115 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Kornblatt, Joyce R. Breaking bread: photocopied proofs, pp 116-247, photocopy of review (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Lapin, Mark. Pledge of allegiance: correspondence, ts of short stories (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Lapin, Mark. Pledge of allegiance: editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Larson, Charles. The insect colony: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Ingram, Kevin. Rebel: photocopied galley proofs, pp 142-342 [legal size] (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Ingram, Kevin. Rebel: stamped, photocopied proofs, pp 1-131 [legal size] (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Ingram, Kevin. Rebel: stamped, photocopied proofs, pp132-245 [legal size] (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Knowles, John. The private life of Axie Reed: photocopied galleys [legal size] (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Knowles, John. A stolen past: galleys [legal size] (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Lish, Gordon. Dear Mr. Capote: photocopied galleys [legal size] (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Lish, Gordon. Peru: photocopied galleys [legal size] (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Lehmann, John. Thrown to the Woolfs: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Lehmann, John. The strange destiny of Rupert Brooke: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - L'Heureux, John. Desires: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Lish, Gordon. Dear Mr. Capote: photocopied ts of "final version," pp 1-162 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Lish, Gordon. Dear Mr. Capote: photocopied ts of "final version," pp 163-313 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Lish, Gordon. Dear Mr. Capote: photocopied ts, pp 1-99, with correspondence (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Lish, Gordon. Dear Mr. Capote: photocopied ts, pp 1-124, with correspondence (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Lish, Gordon. Dear Mr. Capote: photocopied ts, pp 1-61, several alternative pp (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Lish, Gordon. Dear Mr. Capote: photocopied ts, pp 125-253 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Lish, Gordon. Dear Mr. Capote: photocopied ts, pp 1-100 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Lish, Gordon. Dear Mr. Capote: photocopied ts, pp 101-197 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Lish, Gordon. Dear Mr. Capote: photocopied ts, pp 1-166, Anasazi: reader's report (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Littlejohn, David. The last days of Sir Anthony Craven: photocopied ts of proposal, pp 1-115 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Littlejohn, David. The last days of Sir Anthony Craven: photocopied ts, pp 116-228 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Littlejohn, David. Architect: the life and works of Henry Moore: photocopied ts of acknowledgements and introduction, correspondence, photocopies of articles written by Littlejohn (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Littlejohn, David. Architect: the life and works of Henry Moore: editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Littlejohn, David.: miscellaneous correspondence, photocopied ts of book proposal, photocopied newspaper articles and ts of review possibly written by Littlejohn (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Marshall-Andrews, Bob. Palace of wisdom: correspondence, editorial material (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Marshall-Andrews, Bob. Palace of wisdom: editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Mason, Anita. The illusionist: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Mason, Anita. The racket: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - McCarthy, Fiona. Eric Gill: correspondence, editorial material (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - McCarthy, Fiona. Eric Gill: editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - McCullough, David Willis. DearMan: photocopied ts, pp 1-154, unpublished (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - McCullough, David Willis. DearMan: photocopied ts, pp 155-348, unpublished (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - McPhillips, Robert. Joyce Carol Oates, a life: correspondence, photocopied ts of proposal (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Miller, Eleanor.: correspondence regarding book proposal (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Mitford, Jessica. The American way of birth: photocopied ts of notes and sources, photocopies of reviews (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Mitford, Jessica. Daughters and rebels: editorial material, photocopied reviews and articles regarding 1981 re-issue (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Mitford, Jessica. Faces of Philip: photocopied ts, chapters I-IX, some miscellaneous material (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Mitford, Jessica. Faces of Philip: correspondence, also regarding the republishing of Daughters and rebels (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Mitford, Jessica. Grace Darling: photocopied ts of acknowledgement and several chapters, correspondence (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Mitford, Jessica. Grace Darling: editorial material (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Mitford, Jessica.: photocopied ts of two essays, photocopied newspaper articles by Mitford (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Mockler, Anthony. Project G (an unauthorized biography of Graham Greene): photocopied ts of proposal (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Moore, Brian. The black robe: promotional materials, photocopies of reviews (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Moore, Brian. Cold heaven: photocopied ts, pp 1-132 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Brian. Cold heaven: photocopied ts, pp 133-257 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Moore, Brian. Cold heaven: photocopied ts, pp 258-358 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Moore, Brian. The color of blood: photocopied ts, pp 1-115 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Moore, Brian. The color of blood: photocopied ts, pp 116-24 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Moore, Brian. The color of blood: correspondence, editorial material (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Moore, Brian. The color of blood: photocopied reviews and articles regarding author (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Moore, Brian.: correspondence regarding resale rights for The color of blood, photocopies of reviews for: No other life (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Moore, Brian. The statement: photocopies of fax correspondence and editorial material (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Brian. The statement: photocopies of reviews (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Mosel, Tad. Leading lady: the world and theatre of Katherine Cornell: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Mosel, Tad. The Montbanks: photocopied ts of proposal (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Murray, John F. Fighting for life: photocopied ts of sample chapter (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Newman, Robert P. Cold war romance: Lillian Hellman and John Melby: correspondence, photocopied ts, pp 1-124 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Newman, Robert P. Cold war romance: Lillian Hellman and John Melby: photocopied ts, pp 125-262 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Newman, Robert P. Cold war romance: Lillian Hellman and John Melby: photocopied ts, pp 263-417, extra text (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. American appetites: correspondence, editororial material (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. American appetites: photocopies of reviews (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Because it is bitter and because it is my heart: correspondence (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Because it is bitter and because it is my heart: editorial material (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Because it is bitter and because it is my heart: photocopied transcript of radio interview, photocopies of reviews (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Blackwater: correspondence (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Blackwater: phtocopied excerpt appearing in Lear's magazine, September, 1991, photocopy of article by Dominic Dunne, Vanity Fair, October, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Blackwater: photocopies of reviews (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. The Crosswicks horror: correspondence (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, writing as Smith, Rosamond. Double delight: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of review (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Foxfire: photocopied ts of foreword, epilogue, miscellaneous changes and pages, correspondence, editorial material (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Foxfire: photocopies of playboy interview, reviews (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Haunted: photocopied ts of afterword, correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Heat: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of review (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol.: photocopied ts of short stories withdrawn from Heat (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. I lock the door upon myself: correspondence, editorial material, miscellaneous material including award announcements (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. My heart laid bare: correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, writing as Smith, Rosamond. Nemesis: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. The radio astronomer: photocopied short story (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Raven's wing: photocopied ts, pp 1-128 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Raven's wing: photocopied ts, pp 129-274 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Raven's wing: photocopied ts of short stories (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, writing as Smith, Rosamond. Snake eyes: correspondence, editorial, photocopies of reviews (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. the sophisticated cat: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, writing as Smith Rosamond. Soul/mate: correspondence, editorial material (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, writing as Smith Rosamond. Soul/mate: editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. The time traveler: photocopied ts of new or supplemental poems for book, correspondence (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. The time traveler: editorial material (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol.: photocopies of of poem and essay, ts of essay on the death of English poet Philip Larkin; all found in brown envelope with time traveler material (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Unstoppable Oates: correspondence, photocopied ts (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. We were the Mulvaneys: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. What I lived for: correspondence, editorial material, photcopies of interviews (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. What I lived for: photcopies of reviews (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Will you always love me?: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Woman(writer): photocopies of reviews (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, writing as Smith, Rosamond. You can't catch me: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. You must remember this: photocopies of article, reviews (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Zombie: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. 12 plays: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol.: correspondence, 1984-1989 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol.: photocopies of book reviews and articles written by Oakes (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - O'Brien, Tim: Going after Cacciato: correspondence, photocopies of articles about O'Brien (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Packard, Jerrold M. Farewell in splendor: photocopied ts of proposal, prologue, outline of chapters, correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Packard, Jerrold M. Stealing the stones, the passion of Lord Elgin: correspondence, photocopied ts of proposal (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Park, Herbert. At a certain age: photocopied ts of sample pages, correspondence (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Park, Herbert. At a certain age: editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Pearson, John. The serpent and the stag: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Pitcher, George. the dogs who came to stay: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Reidinger, Paul. The best man: photocopied ts (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Reidinger, Paul. The eyes of others: photocopied ts (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Root, Wells. Writing the script: photcopied ts of table of contents, chapter XVII, miscellaneous pp, correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Sandys, Celia. Churchill, wanted dead or alive: photocopied ts (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Sandys, Celia. The young Churchill: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Schlee, Ann. Laing[?]: ts of outline, chapters 1 and 2 of proposed book, correspondence, photocopy of review of other work by author (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Schmidgall, Gary. The stranger Wilde: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Schmidgall, Gary. Walt Whitman, a gay life: bound uncorrected proof (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Schmidgall, Gary. Walt Whitman, a gay life: corrspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Moore, Brian. The black robe: copyedited galleys [legal size] (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Moore, Brian. Cold heaven: photocopied galleys [legal size] (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Moore, Brian. Cold heaven: photocopied galleys [legal size] (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Moore, Brian. The color of blood: photocopied galley proof [legal size] (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol. Raven's wing: photocopied galleys [legal size] (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Reidinger, Paul. The best man: photocopied galleys [legal size] (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Sterling, Claire. The time of the assassins: photocopied page proofs [legal size] (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Sterling, Claire. The time of the assassins: photocopied ts, pp 1-175 [legal size] (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Schmidgall, Gary. Walt Whitman, leaves of grass: ts of proposal for a new edition (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Simmons, Steve. Body blows: photocopied ts, pp 1-160 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Simmons, Steve. Body blows: photocopied ts, pp 161-323 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Simmons, Steve. Body blows: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Sinclair, Murray. F. Scott Fitzgerald, American spy: photocopied ts of author's outline (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Sinclair, Murray. F. Zack and William: photocopied ts of outline and sample chapters [found in Sinclair folder, but may be work of another author] (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Sally. My grandmother's house: photocopied ts of short story; Staying is nowhere: photocopied ts of proposed novel, some correspondence (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Spark, Muriel. Mary Shelley: correspondence concerning Bram Stoker award (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Steegmuller, Francis. Paris and Naples: photocopied ts of foreword and chapters 1-4, correspondence, photocopies of articles and reviews by Steegmuller (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Steegmuller, Francis. Silence at Salerno: photocopied ts, chapter one, some of chapter two (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Steegmuller, Francis. Silence at Salerno: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Stegner, Page. Sportscar menopause:carboned ts pp 264, 260, 282-284, 294, correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Stegner, Page.: correspondence regarding proposed biography of Robinson Jeffers, photocopy of article on Jeffers (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Sterling, Claire. Crime without frontiers: photocopied ts of proposals, correspondence (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Sterling, Claire. The time of the assassins: photocopied ts of outline, notes (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Sterling, Claire. The time of the assassins: editorial material [one of two] (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Sterling, Claire. The time of the assassins: editorial material [two of two] (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Sterling, Claire. The time of the assassins: photocopies of articles written by Sterling, related news articles, interviews, reviews (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Stinnett, Caskie. Grand and private pleasures: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of articles written by Stinnett and under the name of Wolfe, Randolph (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Swaim, Lawrence. Love, by sun and candlelight: photocopies of reader's report and recommendation (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Swaim, Lawrence, and Aziz, Sartaz. Islamic feminism: photocopied ts of an introduction, interview with Azizah Al-Hibri, photocopy of article by authors, correspondence (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Swaim, Lawrence. The killing: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Swaim, Lawrence. Millenium: ts of description, chapter outline, pp 1-125, correspondence (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Swaim, Lawrence. Waiting for the earthquake: correspondence, editorial material, photcopy of review (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Torchia, Joseph. As if after sex: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Tuohy, Frank. The collected stories, correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Tuohy, Frank. Live bait: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Vidal, Gore. Duluth: ts of reader's report, photocopied ts, pp 1-156 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Vidal, Gore. Duluth: photocopied ts, pp 157-331 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Vidal, Gore. Duluth: photocopied ts, pp 1-156 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Vidal, Gore. Duluth: photocopied ts, pp 157-331 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Vidal, Gore. Empire: photocopied review by Richard Poirer (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Willis, Ted. The lion of Judah: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Wooley, Persia. Child of the northern spring: ts (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Yaffee, James. Saul and Morris, worlds apart: correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Zelver, Patricia. A man of middle age: ts of untitled short story, correspondence, editorial material, photocopies of reviews (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified: ts, Part four, The golden gate (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified: photocopied ts of untitled short story (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Sterling, Clare. The time of the assassins: photocopied ts [legal size] (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Feibleman, Peter, and Hellman, Lillian. Eating together:photocopied master proof [oversized legal] (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B. Business correspondence
    - Correspondence: B, 1962-1964 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: D, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: G, 1962-1964 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: J, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: letters from John Lehmann, 1962-1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: M, 1965-1967 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: N, 1962-1964, mostly from Howard Nemerov (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: P, 1963-1967 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: R, 1962-1963 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: S, 1962-1965 (Box 50, Folder 10)